The video fix targets only `.et_pb_video_box` which is specific to the Divi theme. However, the existing CSS in css/et-divi-dynamic-tb-13496-tb-384.css (line 7) shows that `.et_pb_video_box` already has base styles including `display: block`, `position: relative`, and `line-height: 0`.

While this override is more specific and should work, consider whether a more targeted fix would be better. For example, if the issue is specifically with iframes having 0 height, you could add styles that work alongside the existing Divi styles rather than overriding them completely. This would make the fix more resilient to theme updates and reduce the likelihood of unintended side effects.
```suggestion
    width: 100%;
    max-width: 100%;
    height: auto;
    min-height: 300px;
    /* Fallback height if container provides no height */
    aspect-ratio: 16 / 9;
    /* Modern aspect ratio guidance without overriding container */
    display: block;
}

/* Note: Rely on Divi's native .et_pb_video_box layout rules */
```
There is a logical conflict in these CSS rules. Line 22 sets `height: 0` (required for the padding-bottom aspect ratio hack), but lines 7 sets `min-height: 300px` on the child elements. This creates a contradiction where the container has zero height but the children have a minimum height of 300px, which can cause layout issues.

The aspect ratio hack works by setting the container to `height: 0` and using `padding-bottom: 56.25%` to create the height based on width. The child iframes should then use `position: absolute` with `height: 100%` to fill that space. Remove the `min-height: 300px` from lines 7, as it interferes with this technique and the `aspect-ratio` property on line 9 already provides a modern fallback.
These CSS rules for `.fluid-width-video-wrapper` are redundant with the existing inline styles in index.html at lines 6911-6928. The inline styles already define the same aspect ratio technique (padding-bottom: 56.25%, height: 0, absolute positioning for children).

Having duplicate CSS rules in multiple places creates maintainability issues. Consider either removing this duplication or documenting why both are needed. If the inline styles are sufficient, these rules (lines 34-51) can be removed from custom-fixes.css.
```suggestion

```
The excessive use of `!important` declarations throughout this file (appearing on 26 out of 79 lines) is a maintainability concern. While `!important` can be necessary to override inline styles or deeply nested specificity, overusing it makes the CSS harder to maintain and debug.

Consider whether all these `!important` declarations are truly necessary. For example, lines 59-64 apply `!important` to footer background colors, but if these styles are loaded last (after the link at line 6943 of index.html), they should naturally override earlier styles without needing `!important`. Using `!important` as a default approach rather than as a last resort is an anti-pattern that can lead to specificity wars in future modifications.
The footer fix applies a hardcoded dark background color (#2e3842) to force visibility of white text. While this solves the immediate problem of invisible text, it may not match the intended design aesthetic and could override intentional customizations.

Consider a more flexible approach such as:
1. Adding a CSS variable for the footer background color that can be easily customized
2. Using a lighter fallback color that works with both light and dark text
3. Documenting in a comment why this specific color was chosen and whether it matches the original site design

This would make the fix more maintainable and adaptable to future design changes.
